안녕
Hi!
- 피비!
- 왔어?
- Hey!
- Hi!
- 신혼여행은 어땠어?
- 환상이었지
- How was the honeymoon?
- Oh, incredible!
샴페인과 촛불을 켠 저녁 식사에
달밤의 해변 산책까지..
Champagne, candle-lit dinners,
moonlight walks on the beach.
너무 낭만적이었어
It was so romantic.
- 마이크는 어디 있어?
- 병원에 갔어
- Where's Mike?
- He's at the doctor.
여행 내내 볼일을 못봤거든
He didn't poop while we were there.
말하면 안되는 거였는데
Shoot, I wasn't supposed
to tell you that.
다시 말할게
연주회에 갔어
I mean.. Okay, he's at a gig.
그런 연주회라면
절대 가고 싶지 않아
A gig we are definitely not going to.
- 잘왔다, 네 도움이 필요해
- 왜? 무슨 일인데?
- I'm glad you're back. I need your help.
- Oh, why, what's up?
연극 오디션이 있는데
불어를 해야해
I have an audition for this play,
and I have to speak French..
이력서에는 잘하는 걸로
돼있거든
which, according to my resume,
I'm fluent in.
- 이력서에 거짓말을 쓰면 안돼
- 그럼, 당연히 안돼지
- Joey, you shouldn't lie on your resume.
- Yeah, you really shouldn't.
그건 그렇고 1년간의
카이로 발굴은 어떠셨나?
By the way, how was
that yearlong dig in Cairo?
괜찮았어
It was okay.
네가 불어를 하는줄 몰랐어
I did not know you spoke French.
너 정말 섹시하다
You're so sexy.
- 나 도와줄 거지?
- 물론
- Well, so will you help me?
- Sure.
제발 그만해, 이러다 널 덮치겠다
Seriously, stop it.
I'm gonna jump on you.
프렌즈 시즌 10
'조이의 오디션'
- 안녕?
- Hey.
- Hi.
내 앞치마 입고 뭐해?
Why are you wearing my apron?
에리카 줄 과자를 만들어
I'm making cookies for Erica.
이제 나가야해, 1시간 후면
비행기가 도착할 거야
We have to leave soon.
Her plane comes in in about an hour.
사람들에게 소개할때
당신은 내 부인이고
When she gets here, is it okay
if I introduce you two as my wife..
에리카는 내 아이를 가진
여자라고 해도 될까?
and the woman who's
carrying my child?
안돼?
No?
이혼 감이야?
Divorce?
- 안녕?
- Hey.
- 레이첼 어디 있는지 알아?
- 아침 이후로는 못봤어
- You know where Rachel is?
- Haven't seen her since morning.
기가 막혀서, 엠마를 데리고
나랑 30분 전에 만나기로 했어
It's unbelievable. She was supposed
to meet me a half-hour ago with Emma.
- 안돼!
- 왜그래?
- Hey!
- 에리카 줄거야
- 이 많은걸 다 먹이게?
- These are for Erica!
- She's gonna eat all those cookies?
아기가 귀엽고 통통해야 하니까
Well, I want the baby
to come out all cute and fat!
- 에리카는 왜 오는거야?
- 서로 좀더 친해지면 좋잖아
- So why is Erica coming to visit?
- We wanna get to know her better.
뉴욕은 처음이라서
관광지를 구경하고 싶대
She's never been to New York,
so she wants to see the tourist spots:
자유의 여신상이나
엠파이어 스테이트 빌딩 같은곳
Statue of Liberty,
Empire State Building.
전부 사람들이 소떼처럼
득실득실한 곳이야
There's always so many people,
and they're being corralled like cattle.
가끔은 어떤 멍청이가
"음매"하고 울기도 하지
And, you know, there's always
some idiot who goes, "Moo."
그게 짜증나면
자기부터 그만 울어
Well, if it annoys you so much,
then why do you do it?
- 박물관에 데려가봐
- 됐어
- You should take her to a museum.
- Oh, please.
거기 가면 챈들러는
이 말밖에 안할거야
So I can hear Chandler say
over and over again:
"이게 예술이야?
이 정도는 나도 한다"
"You call this art? I could make that."
스폰지로 만든
탑이었으니까 그렇지
It was a tower of sponges.
안녕? 30분이나 늦게
나타나줘서 고마워
Oh, hi. Hi. Thanks for
showing up 30 minutes late.
물론 대단한 이유가 있으시겠지
미장원 예약이 있었어?
No, I'm sure you have a great excuse.
What was it, a hair appointment?
아니면 손발톱 손질?
아니면 백화점 세일이라도 했나?
A mani-pedi?
Was there a sale at Barneys?
아빠가 심장 발작을 일으키셨어
My father had a heart attack.
내가 백화점에 있는 동안에..
While I was at Barneys.
- 이런, 세상에!
- 레이첼..
- Oh, my God, Rach.
- Honey?
- 정말 안됐다
- 괜찮으셔?
- I'm so sorry.
- Is he okay?
괜찮을 거라곤 했지만
아직 의식이 없으셔
Yeah, he's gonna be fine,
but he's heavily sedated.
내가 롱아일랜드에 같이 가줄게
Okay, I'm gonna go
to Long Island with you.
- 혼자 있을순 없잖아
- 아니야, 난 괜찮아
- I mean, you can't be alone right now.
- No, come on, I'm totally okay.
올 필요없어
I don't need you to come.
- 나 혼자 해결할수 있어
- 그래도 내가 가고싶어
- I can totally handle this on my own.
- Still, still, let me come for me.
그래, 정 그렇다면 와
Okay. If you really need to.
모니카가 방금 구운 과자를
먹으면 위로가 될거야
I bet someone could use one
of Monica's freshly baked cookies.
그거 좋겠다
Oh, I really could.
'센트럴 퍼크'
이정도면 아주 간단해
All right, it seems pretty simple.
첫 대사는
'내 이름은 클로드입니다'야
Your first line is,
"My name is Claude."
날 따라해봐
So just repeat after me.
- 다시 한번 해보자
- 좋아
- Well, let's try it again.
- Okay.
내말은..
It's not..
그게 아니었어
quite what I'm saying.
그래? 나한테는 똑같이 들리는데
Really? Sounds exactly the same to me.
- 정말이야?
- 그래
- It does, really?
- Yeah.
- 그냥 다시 해보자
- 좋아
- Let's just try it again.
- Okay.
- 잘들어
- 알았어
- Really listen.
- Got it.
- 얘들아!
- 안녕?
- Hey, you guys!
- Hi.
아주 특별한 사람을 소개할게
I want you to meet
someone really special.
피비, 이쪽은 에리카야
얘는 우리 아기고
Phoebe, this is Erica.
And this is the baby!
- 조이, 에리카와 아기야
- 안녕?
- Joey, Erica, baby.
- Hi.
여러분, 에리카와 아기예요
Everyone, Erica! Baby!
모니카, 진정해, 제발..
Monica. Calm. Self.
- 앉으세요
- 고마워요
- Hey, sit down.
- Thank you.
뵙게 돼서 너무 기뻐요
여기 오다니 실감이 안나요
It's really nice to meet you guys.
I can't believe I'm here.
뉴욕에 잘 오셨어요, 불어로는..
Well, welcome to New York City,
or should I say:
몽쉘통통 뉴욕 시티!
New York City.
웬 헛소리냐?
Why would you say that?
오늘은 뭘 할거예요?
Okay. What are you
gonna be doing today?
전부 다 보고 싶어요, 타임 스퀘어
코니 아일랜드, 록펠러 센터
Well, I wanna see everything! Times
Square, Coney Island, Rockefeller Center.
자유의 여신상 꼭대기에도
걸어 올라가 보세요
You should walk to the top
of the Statue of Liberty.
- 그래요, 그렇게 해요
- 좋죠
- Oh, yeah, let's do that.
- Great.
괜찮은 애가 안나오기만 해봐라
This baby better be really good.
저희 아버지를 만나러 왔어요
전 레이첼 그린이에요
Hi. Excuse me, I'm here to see my
father. My name is Rachel Green.
- 저는 닥터 로스 겔러고요
- 로스, 여긴 병원이야
- And I'm Dr. Ross Geller.
- Ross, please, this is a hospital.
여기서의 닥터들은
중요한 사람들이라고
That actually means something here.
- 들어가도 될까요?
- 물론이죠
- So can we please go in?
- Absolutely.
난 밖에서 기다리는게 좋겠어
Rach, I think I'm gonna
wait out here..
목이 좀 따끔거리는데
아버님께 옮으면 안되잖아
because my throat is feeling a little
scratchy. I don't wanna infect him.
- 로스, 아빠를 무서워하지마
- 무서운게 아니라 정말 아파
- Ross, please. Don't be so scared of him.
- I am not scared of him. I'm really sick.
- 약 때문에 의식이 없으세요
- 이제 나아진것 같다
- He's under sedation, so he's out.
- I'm feeling better.
맙소사!
Oh, my God.
귀랑 코털 정리기를 사드렸는데
통 안쓰시나 보네
That ear and nose hair trimmer I got him
was just money down the drain, huh?
그린양? 아버님 주치의께서
통화하시고 싶답니다
Ms. Green? Your father's doctor's on
the phone if you'd like to speak to him.
네, 그러죠, 괜찮겠어?
Oh, great. Are you gonna be okay?
- 의식도 없으신데 뭐, 괜찮아
- 알았어
- He's unconscious. We'll be just fine.
- Okay.
- TV 때문에 깨셨어요?
- 아니
- Did the TV wake you?
- No.
자네가 침대에 발을 올려서
도뇨관이 빠졌네
When you put your feet up on my bed,
you tugged on my catheter.
여긴 웬일인가?
What are you doing here, Geller?
레이첼과 함께 왔어요
곧 돌아 올겁니다
Well, I came with Rachel,
who should be back any second.
- 별일 없으셨어요?
- 심장 마비가 왔었지
- So, what's new?
- Oh, I had a little heart attack.
많이 고통스러우세요?
Right. Is it painful?
심장 마비가?
아니면 자네와 얘기하는게?
What, the heart attack
or sitting here talking to you?
레이첼을 불러와야겠군요
Let's see if we can get
that Rachel back in here.
자네는 별일 없었나?
내 딸 중에 또 건드린 애는 없고?
So, what's new with you? Knocked up
any more of my daughters lately?
아뇨, 한명뿐이죠, 레이첼!
Nope. Just the one. Rach!
아빠, 일어나셨군요
Daddy, hi. You're awake.
- 어떠세요?
- 괜찮다
- How are you?
- I'm okay.
그나저나 로스 덕분에
큰 위안이 됐다
By the way, Ross has been
of great comfort.
며칠 더 입원하셔야 한대요
They want to keep you here
for a couple more nights.
알아요
I know.
집에가서 아빠 짐을 가져올게요
But I'm gonna go home
and get a bunch of your stuff..
그래야 편히 계시죠
so that you're really comfortable.
고맙다
Oh, thank you, sweetheart.
별일이 다 있죠?
It's pretty ironic, huh?
심장 전문의가
심장 마비에 걸리시다니요
You being a heart surgeon,
and you had a heart attack.
저로 따지면 '알로사우루스'에게
먹히는 꼴이잖아요
It'd be like if I was eaten
by an Allosaurus.
전 밖에서 기다릴게요
I'm gonna wait outside.
의식이 없긴 뭐가 없어요?
"He's pretty much out."
아니야!
No!
그럼 쪼개서 해보자
Okay, maybe if we just break it down.
한 음절씩 끊어서 말할게
날 따라해봐
Okay, let's try it one syllable at a time.
Okay, so repeat after me.
좋았어, 이제 빨리해봐
Great! Okay, faster.
- 도저히 못 가르치겠어
- 뭐하는 거야?
- Okay, it's too hard. I can't teach you.
- What are you doing?
네 머리를 벽에
처박기 전에 가야겠어
I have to go before I put
your head through a wall.
가지마, 네가 필요해
오디션은 내일이란 말이야!
Don't go, I need you!
My audition is tomorrow!
저녁을 만들려고 했는데
Hey. I was gonna
make us some dinner..
냉장고에 베이컨과
생크림 밖에 없어
but all I found in your dad's fridge
was bacon and heavy cream.
심장 마비가 왜 왔는지 알만하다
I think we solved the mystery
of the heart attack.
- 부모님께 전화해봤어?
- 응, 엠마는 잘있대
- Did you call your parents?
- Oh, yeah. Emma's doing great.
잘됐네
Oh, good.
- 왜?
- 실감이 안나
- What?
- I just can't believe..
레이첼 그린의 방에 들어왔다는게
I'm in Rachel Green's room.
- 전에도 와봤잖아
- 와본거 좋아하네
- You've been in my room before.
- Yeah, sure, right.
내가 언제 레이첼 그린의
방에 와봤겠어?
Like I'd ever be
in Rachel Green's room.
자꾸 성을 붙여서 부르니까
너무 이상한거 알지?
Okay, I gotta tell you, it's really weird
when you use my whole name.
미안
Sorry.
- 괜찮아?
- 응
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- 힘든 하루였지?
- 맞아
- Yeah, you had a rough day.
- Yeah.
아빠의 그런 모습 너무 이상해
아빠는 의사시잖아
It's just so weird seeing him like that,
you know? I mean, he's a doctor.
의사가 병이 날거라곤
생각도 못했어
You don't expect doctors to get sick.
우리도 아플때가 있지
But we do.
괜찮으실 거야
He's gonna be okay, Rach.
혼자 깨어나시게 하긴 싫어
병원에 가봐야겠어
I don't want him to wake up alone.
I should go to the hospital.
- 안돼, 기다려봐
- 왜?
- What? No, no. Hey, hey, look.
- What?
지금은 약물에 취해계신 상태라서
They gave him a lot of medication.
네가 곁에 있어도 모르실 거야
He wouldn't even know
if you were there.
내일 아침 일찍 가보자
We'll go see him first thing
in the morning.
- 죄책감 느낄 필요 없을까?
- 물론이지
- Really? I shouldn't feel guilty?
- No.. God, hey.
넌 훌륭한 딸이었어
Rach, you've been an
amazing daughter, okay?
- 지금은 좀 쉬어
- 네 말이 맞아
- Right now you need to get some rest.
- Okay, maybe you're right.
잘자
Good night.
잠깐만!
Wait, wait, wait.
나랑 잠시 같이 있어 줄래?
Would you stay here with me
for a little while?
- 좋아
- 그래
- Sure.
- Okay.
- 같이 와줘서 정말 고마워
- 물론이지
- Thank you for coming with me today.
- Oh, of course.
레이첼 그린은 네가
자기 방에 있어서 기쁘대
Rachel Green is very happy
you're in her room.
나도야, 이리와
Me too. Come here.
오늘밤은 혼자 있기 싫어
I just don't wanna be alone tonight.
그럼 내가 침낭을
갖고 오거나, 아니면..
Okay, well, I can maybe grab
a sleeping bag or..
안돼, 레이첼!
No, Rach!
미안해, 이건 좋은 생각이
아닌것 같아
I'm sorry, I just don't
think this is a good idea.
해보기 전에는 모르는 일이잖아
Well, we won't know that
until we do it, will we?
레이첼..
Look..
넌 아버지 일로 상심했고
마음이 약해져 있어
You are upset about your father,
and you're feeling vulnerable..
이러면 안될것 같아
and I just don't feel
it would be right.
이러면 널 이용하는게 되잖아
I feel like I'd be, you know,
taking advantage of you.
이용은 무슨?
내가 기회를 줄테니까 맘껏 즐겨
What..? Taking advantage? I am giving
you the advantage. Enjoy!
물론 그렇게 되면 아주 좋겠지
Look, I'm sure it would be great..
하지만 둘중 하나는
정신을 차려야해
but I think one of us
has to be thinking clearly.
그러니 내가 갈게
So I'm gonna go.
알았어
Okay.
내일 아침에 봐
I'll see you in the morning.
4개월간 한번도 못했는데
어디서 상 안주나?
I haven't had sex in four months.
I should get a medal for that!
안내해 주셔서 너무 감사해요
정말 재미있었어요
Thanks so much for taking me
to all those places. I had a great time.
나도 기뻐요, 그리고 챈들러 일은
정말 미안해요
I'm glad. Listen, I wanna apologize
about Chandler, though.
- 이렇게 될줄 몰랐어요
- 뉴욕은 굉장해!
- I just did not see this coming.
- New York is awesome!
- 대체 왜그래?
- 전에 가봤던 곳이지만
- What is with you?
- I've been to these places before..
제대로 본적이 없었어
but I've never really seen them.
"음매"하고 우느라
볼시간이 없었지
Yeah, you miss a lot
when you're mooing.
브로드웨이 쇼를 보러가자
'캐츠' 어때?
Let's go to a Broadway show. Cats!
이제 그만하자
I think we've done enough.
그 쇼에선 고양이 옷을 입은
배우들이 사람처럼 노래를 해
Honey, these are actors dressed like cats
who sing like people.
재미있잖아!
I mean, come on!
- 구경 시켜주셔서 감사해요
- 저희가 즐거웠죠
- Thank you for showing me around.
- Oh, it was our pleasure.
에리카를 잘 알게 돼서
너무 좋아요
We're so much enjoying
getting to know you.
더 알고 싶은게 있으면
물어 보세요
Well, if there's anything else
you wanna know..
좋아요
Okay.
아기 아버지에 대해
질문해도 될까요?
Can we ask you some
questions about the father?
물론이죠
Oh, sure. Yeah.
고등학교때 남자 친구였어요
풋볼팀 주장이고 아주 귀여웠죠
Well, he was my high-school boyfriend,
captain of the football team, really cute.
- 장학금을 받고 대학에 갔어요
- 잘됐군요
- Got a scholarship and went to college.
- That's great.
아마 그 애가 맞을 거예요
Yeah, it's almost definitely him.
무슨 소리죠?
How's that, now?
다른 사람일 수도 있거든요
Well, there's a chance
it's another guy.
그동안 딱 두명과 했는데
I mean, I've only ever been
with two guys..
둘이 묘하게 겹쳤죠
but they sort of overlapped.
그 친구는 뭘 하는데요?
So, what does the other guy do?
- 대학은 갔나요?
- 아뇨, 감옥에 있어요
- Does he go to college too?
- No, he's in prison.
누명이라도 썼나요?
Was he falsely accused of something?
그게 아니라..
No.
삽으로 아버지를 쳐죽였어요
He killed his father with a shovel.
그것만 빼면 참 좋은 아이죠
Other than that, he's a great guy.
그 친구 아버지는
그렇게 생각하지 않을걸요
I'll bet his dad doesn't think so.
- 안자?
- 당연히 안자지
- Are you awake?
- Of course I'm awake.
아마 이제부터 영원히 못잘걸
Assume from now on
that I'm always awake.
그애가 확실한지도 모르잖아
풋볼 선수일 수도 있어
All right, we don't know that it's him.
I mean, it could be the football guy.
우리가 누구야?
분명히 삽질한 놈일걸
Honey, it's us.
Of course it's the shovel killer.
좋아, 그 애라고 쳐
Well, all right,
let's say that it is him.
그래도 저 아기가
싫은건 아니잖아
Would we not want the baby? No.
- 그렇다고 애를 다르게 대할래?
- 계속 주시는 해야지
- Would we treat him any differently?
- I'd keep an eye on him.
애 아빠가 누군지
반드시 알아내야해
We have to find out
who the father is.
- 어떻게?
- 나도 몰라
- How?
- I don't know.
- 테스트 해보면 알잖아
- 우리가 오버하는 걸지도 몰라
- They have tests for these things, right?
- Yes, but maybe we're just overreacting.
당신은 말하기 쉽겠지
놈은 아버지를 죽였으니까
Easy for you to say.
He's a father killer.
그놈은 아마 엄마는
사랑했을 거야
He probably loves his mommy.
삽질하던 팔에는
'엄마'라는 문신도 있을걸
He's probably got a tattoo that says
"Mom" on his shovel-wielding arm.
이제 1부터 5까지 세어봅시다
We'll now count from one to five.
- 잘하셨습니다
- 고맙습니다
- Good job.
- Thank you.
- 피비
- 안녕, 조이?
- Hey.
- Hey, Joey.
어제 일이 맘에 걸려서
많이 생각해봤어
Listen, I feel really badly about
yesterday, and I thought about it a lot.
내가 너무 성급했나봐
다시 시작해보자
No, I was too impatient.
So let's try it again.
괜찮아, 안도와줘도 돼
That's okay. I don't need your help.
나 혼자 독학했어
이제 어느 정도는 할줄 알지
I worked on it myself,
and I gotta say I am pretty good.
- 그럼 들어봐도 될까?
- 물론이지
- Really, can I hear some of it?
- Sure, sure.
좋아
Okay.
봤지?
See?
그, 그건..
You, you're not..
그건..
You're not.. You're..
정말로 불어가 아니라니까!
Again, you're not speaking French!
불어 맞아, 그리고 난
반드시 그 역을 딸수 있어
Oh, well, I think I am. Yeah, and I think
I'm definitely gonna get the part.
그게 어떻게 가능해?
How could you possibly think that?
테이프 속의 남자는
나한테 잘한다고 했어
The guy on the tape said
I was doing a good job!
나도 커피좀 줄래?
Hey, Rach, can you grab me
a cup of coffee?
그래
Sure.
아침 내내 조용한데 무슨일 있어?
You've been quiet all morning.
Is everything okay?
- 정말 괜찮아?
- 그럼
- You sure you're all right?
- Yep.
좋아
Okay.
난 가서 아침을 사올게
Well, I'm gonna go
grab us some breakfast.
- 혹시나 해서 말인데
- 이제 나오시는군
- FYI.
- There it is.
앞으로는..
In the future..
여자가 동정 어린
섹스를 요구하면, 그냥 해
when a girl asks for some
ill-advised sympathy sex, just do it.
잠깐, 어젯밤 일 때문에
화가 난거야?
Wait, wait, you're mad at me
about last night?
- 난 옳은 일을 한것 뿐이야
- 그래?
- I was just trying to do the right thing.
- Really?
네가 옳은 일을 했다면
If you had done the right thing..
오늘 아침 난
자괴감과 수치심 대신
I wouldn't have woken up
feeling stupid and embarrassed.
편안함과 만족감을 느끼며
깨어났겠지
I would've woken up feeling
comforted and satisfied.
- 글쎄..
- 됐어!
- Well..
- Oh, stop that!
정말 너무 한다
난 착한 남자가 되려고 한거야
I can't believe this.
I was just being a good guy.
널 존중하고 이해하려고
노력했다고
I treated you with
respect and understanding.
그거 정말 섹시하네
Oh, that is so hot.
널 위해서 한 일이야
Hey, I was looking out for you.
그래? 이거알아? 난 어른이야
Oh, really? Well, you know what?
I am a big girl.
내게 뭐가 좋은지
충고해줄 필요는 없다고
I don't need someone telling me
what is best for me.
그동안 섹스를 마다한 적은
많았지만 이번이 최악이었어
I gotta say, I've not had sex a lot
of times before. This is the worst ever!
그러셔? 나도 그리 좋진 않았네요
Oh, really? Really?
Well, it wasn't very good for me either.
좋아, 그럼 이렇게 하자
Okay, you know..?
Hey, hey, you know what?
앞으로 이런 일을 피하기 위해
To avoid this little thing
in the future..
앞으로 우리 둘은
절대로 섹스를 하지 말자
let's just say you and me?
Never having sex again.
- 뭐?
- 그래, 섹스는 물 건너갔어
- What?
- That's right! Sex is off the table!
너랑은 다신 섹스 안 해!
I am never having sex with you again!
좀 나아지셨나요, 닥터 그린?
Dr. Green, are you feeling better?
- 점심 어땠어?
- 너무 즐거웠어요
- Hey. How was lunch?
- We had a good time.
그런데 부탁이 있어요
By the way, I wanted
to ask you something.
뱃속의 아이가 아들이라면
이름을 지을때
It would really mean a lot to me
if the baby was a boy..
저희 아버지 이름을 따서
that you name him after my father..
지미니 빌리 밥으로 해주세요
Jiminy Billy Bob.
- 정말로요?
- 아뇨!
- Oh, really?
- No!
모니카 말이 맞네요, 재미있었어요
You were right. That was fun.
전 가서 짐을 쌀게요
I'm gonna go finish packing.
- 테스트를 해보겠대?
- 아니, 할 필요없어
- So is she gonna take the test?
- No, she doesn't have to.
- 애 아빠가 누군지 알아냈어
- 맙소사
- I found out who the father is.
- Oh, God.
- 그 삽질한 놈이지?
- 아니야
- It's Shovely Joe, isn't it?
- No, it's not.
어떻게 알아?
How do you know?
에리카가 성교육 시간에
열심히 안들은 모양이야
Erica didn't pay attention
in sex ed class..
그 감옥에 있다는 애랑
한일 가지고는
because the things she did
with that prison guy?
애가 생기기 힘들겠더라고
It'd be pretty hard to make
a baby that way.
뭔데? 우리가 거의 안하는거?
아님 절대 안하는거?
Oh, God, what was it? The thing we
hardly ever do, or the thing we never do?
우리가 절대 안하는거
The thing we never do.
그녀석, 제대로 삽질했네
Shovely Joe.
'나트 혼 극장
더글라스 페어뱅크스 극장'
- 준비되면 시작하세요
- 알겠습니다
- Whenever you're ready, Joey.
- Right.
- 미안하지만 뭐하는 거죠?
- 그냥 편하게 불어로 해요
- I'm sorry, what's going on?
- Dude, come on, French it up.
조이, 불어를 할줄 아나요?
Joey, do you speak French?
그건 불어가 아닙니다
That's not French.
그것도 아니에요
Neither is that.
오디션을 그만 끝내겠습니다
You know what?
I think this audition is over.
실례합니다
Excuse me?
저는 레진 필란지예요
I am Regine Phalange.
지나가다가 저분이
말씀하시는걸 들었는데
I was passing by when
I heard this man speaking..
저희 고향 '에스티 로더'의
방언을 하시더군요
the regional dialect of my
French town of Estee Lauder.
이분이 하시는게
불어가 맞다고요?
You really think this man
is speaking French?
들어 보세요
사실을 말씀 드릴게요
이 사람은 제 오빠예요
오빠는..
조금 모자라죠
오빠 말에 그냥
맞장구 쳐주실수 없나요?
잘했어요, 조이
Good job, little buddy.
훌륭한 불어 실력입니다
That was some really good French.
하지만 배역은 다른 분에게
드려야 할듯 하군요
But I think we're gonna go
with someone else for the part.
- 좋아요, 아무튼 불어는 잘했죠?
- 훌륭했어요
- All right, but my French was good?
- It was great.
봤지?
See?
- 엠마는 잠들었어
- 잘됐네
- Emma's down for the night.
- Oh, good.
- 난 이만 가볼게
- 그래
- So I guess I'm gonna take off.
- Okay.
잠깐, 가기 전에..
Hey, listen, just before you go..
나랑 같이 있어줘서
고맙다는 말을 하고 싶어
I just wanna say thank you
for coming with me.
천만에
Oh, no problem.
그리고 있잖아..
And also, you know, I..
아까 네가 섹스에 대해
한 얘기 생각해 봤는데
I was thinking about what you said,
you know, about the whole sex thing..
또 다시 시작하는건
좋은 생각이 아닌것 같아
Probably not a great idea
to go down that road again.
고마워, 같은 생각이라니 기쁘다
Thank you. I'm glad you agree.
아쉽긴해
전에 했을땐 꽤 좋았잖아
It's a shame, though.
When we did it, it was pretty good.
맞아
Yeah.
그건 그래
Yeah, that's true.
정말로 좋았던 그날 기억나?
Hey, do you remember
that one really great time?
- 맞아
- 그렇지?
- Oh, yeah!
- You know?
- 발렌타인 데이였지
- 네 생일이었어
- It was Valentine's Day.
- It was your birthday.
- 아, 맞다
- Oh, yeah.
하긴, 다 지난 일이지
Well, I guess that's all
in the past now.
- 한번이라도 안돼
- 절대 안되지
- Not even one more time.
- Not even once.
- 아무리 원해도 말이야
- 우리가 아무리..
- No matter how much we want it.
- Even if we want it..
- 간절히 원해도 말이야
- 그렇게 결정했지
- really bad.
- That's what we decided.
그래
Right.
- 조금 힘들긴 할거야
- 맞아
- It's kind of hard, though. You know?
- Yeah.
두사람의 마음이
통했는데도, 그렇다면 그건..
When two people have a connection,
you know, that's..
왠지..
Just seems like..
조금..
such a..
낭비 같아
waste.
낭비하긴 싫은데
I hate waste.
- 로스?
- 응?
- Ross?
- Yes?
그러니까..
Just so you know..
우리 사이는..
with us..
절대 물 건너가지 않아
it's never off the table.
젠장, 물 건너갈 일이 없다니
Damn it, it's never off the table.
- 탭 댄스 출 줄 알아?
- 아니
- Okay, can you really tap-dance?
- No.
그럼 지워야 해
It's off the resume.
- 양궁은?
- 못해
- Archery?
- No.
- 승마는?
- 무지하게 떨어지겠지
- Horseback riding?
- Would fall off a lot.
10초 안에 우유 3.79L를
마실수 있어?
You can drink a gallon of milk
in 10 seconds?
그건 할수 있어
That I can do.
그 많은걸 10초에 다 마신다고?
Come on, you can drink
a gallon of milk in 10 seconds?
좋아, 보여 주지
All right, watch me.
- 시간을 재, 준비 됐지?
- 준비, 시작!
- Okay, you time me, ready?
- Ready, go!
성공이야!
You did it!